artician.com 2017-12-31

# Privacy Policy - Elite Push

**Privacy Policy**

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the http://elitepush.com and Elite Push Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Elite Push Inc. include http://elitepush.com and Elite Push. The Elite Push website is a Videos, Courses, Webinars, Articles, Guides, Business Coaching, Inspiration, E-commerce site. By using the Elite Push website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

Elite Push may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Elite Push’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Elite Push. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Elite Push website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Elite Push’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Elite Push encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Elite Push so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Elite Push is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Elite Push website.

**Use of your Personal Information**

Elite Push collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Elite Push may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Elite Push and its affiliates. Elite Push may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Elite Push does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Elite Push may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Elite Push, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Elite Push may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Elite Push, in order to determine what Elite Push services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Elite Push to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Elite Push will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Elite Push or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Elite Push; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Elite Push, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**

The Elite Push website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Elite Push pages, or register with Elite Push site or services, a cookie helps Elite Push to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Elite Push website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Elite Push features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Elite Push services or websites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**

Elite Push secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Children Under Thirteen**

Elite Push does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Disconnecting your Elite Push Account from Third Party Websites**

You will be able to connect your Elite Push account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR ELITE PUSH ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Must login into 3rd party website to account settings and disconnect access..

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Elite Push by contacting us here:

– Web page: http://elitepush.com/contact

– Email:info@elitepush.com

– Phone: 267-800-PUSH

**Changes to this Statement**

Elite Push will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Elite Push encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Elite Push is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

Elite Push welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Elite Push has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Elite Push at:

**Elite Push Inc.**  
1339 E. Berks St  
Philadelphia, Pennsylvania 19125

**Email Address:**  
info@elitepush.com

**Telephone number:  
**267-800-PUSH

Effective as of April 01, 2016
